<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-29T23:50:24+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">LCF</title><subtitle>Creating Dream Worlds</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Building our imagination in real world</title><link href="/article/building-our-imagination-in-real-world" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Building our imagination in real world" /><published>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/building-our-imagination-in-real-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/building-our-imagination-in-real-world">&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-idea&quot;&gt;The Idea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our imagination we can create anything. 
We can build, rebuild, destroy any number of times. 
But is the real world we have always been limited. 
In the real world we lack the freedom to create anything we imagine. 
What if we can actually create the real world from scratch using just our mind? 
Will it be an exciting world? 
The world where anyone can build their dream world! 
Here we will build the tech that will allow us to do just that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;building-reality-step-by-step&quot;&gt;Building Reality: Step by Step&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of our imagination, there are many objects, living beings(trees, animals, humans, plants), roads, buildings, wind, water, machines, etc. Tech to create all of this can’t be build in one step. We propose that first step will be to build the infrastructure part (Buildings, roads, terrains, etc). Now complete buildings, roads, are very complex. So first step is to be able to build simple shapes like cuboid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-build-simple-structures-with-mind&quot;&gt;How to build simple structures with mind?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suppose, if there are some small blocks( maybe nanobots) that we can control from mind, and they can join together to build simple shapes (cuboid, pyramid, plane). For now we can build big blocks (few mm), that will self arrange into shapes when instructed by some machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parts-of-block-architecture&quot;&gt;Parts of block architecture&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Block can assume properties of any material. (Strength, lustre, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Control blocks with mind.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What will be the Structure and machinery of blocks?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Different types of connection leads to different levels of flexibility and strength.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Material of blocks?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;goal-1&quot;&gt;Goal 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 5 blocks. We build a simple structure in computer. There is some device that sends some EM signal to the blocks following some protocol. Upon receiving the signal, the blocks join together in the shape that we have build in our computer model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;further-goals&quot;&gt;Further goals&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reduce size of block.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Impoving connections between blocks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work on controlling blocks through mind&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improving security of software, so that only authorised person or machine can control the block.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blocks-as-universal-material&quot;&gt;Blocks as universal material&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No need to build different material for house, bridge, car, mat, chair, wire, etc. Over time blocks will become robust enough, they will be capable of assuming properties of any material and build anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can be used in construction of large scale structures in space without any 3D printers and human assistance. Machines will mine asteroids, produce blocks, blocks will join to build structures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like there is soil everywhere, what if there are these blocks everywhere and we can build anything with our minds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will make many 3D printers obsolete&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;easily-terraform-planets&quot;&gt;Easily Terraform Planets&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can send machines to other planets, deserts, etc, that will consume the resources available there and produce these blocks. We can then simple send instructions from here, and fully developed cities will be build for us in few days. Or we can simple go there and build whatever we imagine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sources-of-inspiration&quot;&gt;Sources of inspiration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nanobots, nanotech, Iron man suit in infinity war, MIT self joining bots, Neuralink, Exotic and special materials,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/hI5UDKaWJOo&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/hI5UDKaWJOo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mit.edu/2019/self-transforming-robot-blocks-jump-spin-flip-identify-each-other-1030&quot;&gt;Self-transforming robot blocks jump, spin, flip, and identify each other&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://people.csail.mit.edu/sclaici/pdf/romanishin20153d.pdf&quot;&gt;3D M-Blocks: Self-reconfiguring Robots Capable of Locomotion via Pivoting in Three Dimensions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mliWJ_HbQHQ&quot;&gt;Iron Man Suit Infinity War&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wevolver.com/wevolver.staff/m-blocks/&quot;&gt;https://www.wevolver.com/wevolver.staff/m-blocks/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.824.7275&amp;amp;rep=rep1&amp;amp;type=pdf&quot;&gt;M-Blocks: Momentum-driven, Magnetic Modular Robots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Anuroop Singh</name></author><category term="New Ideas" /><category term="Robotics" /><summary type="html">The Idea In our imagination we can create anything. We can build, rebuild, destroy any number of times. But is the real world we have always been limited. In the real world we lack the freedom to create anything we imagine. What if we can actually create the real world from scratch using just our mind? Will it be an exciting world? The world where anyone can build their dream world! Here we will build the tech that will allow us to do just that.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rich dad, Poor Dad” advice to become rich?</title><link href="/article/rich-dad-poor-dad-advice-to-become-rich-bfswl" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rich dad, Poor Dad&quot; advice to become rich?" /><published>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/rich-dad-poor-dad-advice-to-become-rich-bfswl</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/rich-dad-poor-dad-advice-to-become-rich-bfswl">&lt;p&gt;You often say sometime that you don’t want to live this kind bad life where you don’t live for yourself. You want freedom to live life as you want.
Everyone want to become rich ,live luxiourious life, travel around the world but they didn’t know where should they start or what should they do that could make him rich and became independent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here, is the &lt;strong&gt;“Rich dad, Poor Dad”&lt;/strong&gt; advice to become rich and earn more money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“True learning takes power, energy and burning desire and Anger is a big part of that formula”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Rich dad, Poor Dad, He primarily focus on 4 skills that make you to understand how the money works and after that you will become Independent. I’ll keep it super simple to understand what are these:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Accounting&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Investing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Understanding markets&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The law:
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Tax advantage&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Protection from lawsuits.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;accounting&quot;&gt;Accounting:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accounting is the financial literacy  or the ability to read numbers. this is most important skill if you want to become rich. The More you generate money, the more accuracy you required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;investing&quot;&gt;Investing:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the idea of ‘‘money making money”. This involve strategies and formula which multiply you money to make more money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;understanding-markets&quot;&gt;Understanding markets:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the science of supply and demand. In this, You need to know the technical aspects of the market which are emotion driven. Means, Does an investment makes more sense or not based ont he current market conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-law-&quot;&gt;The law:-&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The law is the awareness of accounting corporate, state and federal regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-tax-advantage&quot;&gt;1. Tax advantage:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this, A corporation can do many things than a person can’t  like pay expenses before pay taxes. Means in Basic terms, A rich man buy an “assest” first and then whatever is left on, they pay taxes on it while a normal person pay taxes first and live on what is left after pay tax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-protection-from-lawsuits&quot;&gt;2. Protection from lawsuits:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its s file folder with some legal document that creates a legal document in it. 
For example: when someone filed against a wealthy individual they are often met with layers  of legal protection and often find that the wealthy person actually owns nothing. they control everything , but own nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If, you really want to be rich the only thing you can do is expand your Knowledge. Knowledge in the field of financial terms. If you understand those terms soon you started  to realize that you grow your financial status. NOt so fast, but yeah! it’s started. and you continued to followed your dream path acheive whatever you want in life.
Remember, Knowledge is power. If you got this then YOu are the powerful one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Krishana Kumar</name></author><category term="Business" /><summary type="html">You often say sometime that you don’t want to live this kind bad life where you don’t live for yourself. You want freedom to live life as you want. Everyone want to become rich ,live luxiourious life, travel around the world but they didn’t know where should they start or what should they do that could make him rich and became independent.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Configuring mpv player - no border, loop and saving position on quit</title><link href="/article/configuring-mpv-player-no-border-loop-and-saving-position-on-quit-e94bi" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Configuring mpv player - no border, loop and saving position on quit" /><published>2020-07-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/configuring-mpv-player-no-border-loop-and-saving-position-on-quit-e94bi</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/configuring-mpv-player-no-border-loop-and-saving-position-on-quit-e94bi">&lt;p&gt;mpv is one of the best video players on Linux. Its available on Windows and Mac also.  Lets find out how we can configure this awesome video player:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two different methods:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-command-line-set-everytime-you-use&quot;&gt;1. Command line (set everytime you use)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;-no-border&quot;&gt;* No border&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ mpv --no-border video.mp4
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;-video-loop&quot;&gt;* Video loop&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ mpv --loop video.mp4
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-edit-config-file-set-once-and-for-all&quot;&gt;2. Edit config file (set once and for all)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Using your preferred text editor (like vim), open the file &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/home/$USER/.config/mpv/mpv.conf&lt;/code&gt;. 
If this file does not exists, create it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add following code to the file &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;mpv.conf&lt;/code&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;loop=yes #Playing video will loop
border=no #Remove border
save-position-on-quit=yes #Save last position of playing video
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Save the file, close it, and restart mpv player.
Now it should be as you wanted. Enjoy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Anuroop Singh</name></author><category term="Tutorial" /><summary type="html">mpv is one of the best video players on Linux. Its available on Windows and Mac also. Lets find out how we can configure this awesome video player:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What are domain names, how do they work and how to get one</title><link href="/article/what-are-domain-names-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-get-one-mwc9t" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What are domain names, how do they work and how to get one" /><published>2020-06-19T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/what-are-domain-names-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-get-one-mwc9t</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/what-are-domain-names-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-get-one-mwc9t">&lt;p&gt;We have seen lots of branded domain names like google.com, facebook.com . This site also have a domain name &lt;a href=&quot;https://letscreatefuture.com&quot;&gt;letscreatefuture.com&lt;/a&gt; . So what is the deal, and what are domain names, especially new domain names like .io, .photo, .website or even .me so much used these days?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this article, i want to explain what are domain names and answer some of the most common questions related to them. Here you will learn:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is a domain name?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is DNS (Domain Name System)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Difference between URL, domain name, sub domain, and domain extension.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are uses of domain names.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Where can you buy domain names&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-a-domain-name&quot;&gt;What is a domain name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the real world every house and location has an address, in the same way on internet a domain name is the address of your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Domain names are addresses of places on internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-do-we-need-domain-names&quot;&gt;Why do we need domain names?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want your own website, you are going to need a domain name. By entering the domain name in the browser someone will reach your website. Thats a address of your website which anyone can remember. Thats why people choose memorable domain names so that many people remember it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Your domain name is the first point of contact between you brand and your customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;example-of-domain-name&quot;&gt;Example of domain name&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some examples are www.google.com, emroline.com, facebook.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-do-domain-names-work&quot;&gt;How do domain names work?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using DNS domain names resolve yo IP address of the host that has the website running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-get-a-domain-name&quot;&gt;How to get a domain name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can go to any domain name provider website and buy a domain name. Some famous providers are godaddy, namecheap and epik.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a link for epik.com where you can buy domain names at cheapest possible price:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epik.com/?affid=mi1be1bi1&quot;&gt;Buy domain at lowest price on epik.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anuroop Singh</name></author><category term="Tutorial" /><summary type="html">We have seen lots of branded domain names like google.com, facebook.com . This site also have a domain name letscreatefuture.com . So what is the deal, and what are domain names, especially new domain names like .io, .photo, .website or even .me so much used these days?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What are the keys to start your own business?</title><link href="/article/how-to-start-your-own-business-51qez" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What are the keys to start your own business?" /><published>2020-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/how-to-start-your-own-business-51qez</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/how-to-start-your-own-business-51qez">&lt;p&gt;Hey Entrepreneurs!!! 
Do you want to start something more creative that makes you different from the rest or you want to start the small  business. Everyone of you  have got their own idea. Your idea is in your mind, diary, and desk too and It’s flooded everywhere but you didn’t understand how did you get started with your own idea.  May be you think!! How did you get the capital for your idea, what are the requirements that fulfill your idea, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uhh f**k this!!!!!!! Don’t think too much that makes you feel horrible. In simple word’s due to your fear you didn’t start work on your own idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here, Some of the most important keys to start your own business. I’ll keep it simple. So, let’s start…….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Observation&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Understanding&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Apply it&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything is secondary if you didn’t start working on your own idea. So, don’t keep in mind. You’re smarter than you think you are. Just go and start work on your ideas because nobody gives you a damn shit about your ideas.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Krishana Kumar</name></author><category term="Business" /><summary type="html">Hey Entrepreneurs!!! Do you want to start something more creative that makes you different from the rest or you want to start the small business. Everyone of you have got their own idea. Your idea is in your mind, diary, and desk too and It’s flooded everywhere but you didn’t understand how did you get started with your own idea. May be you think!! How did you get the capital for your idea, what are the requirements that fulfill your idea, and much more.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What should be the right mindset of first time Entrepreneur?</title><link href="/article/what-should-be-the-right-mindset-of-first-time-entrepreneur-k9q2z" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What should be the right mindset of first time Entrepreneur?" /><published>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/what-should-be-the-right-mindset-of-first-time-entrepreneur-k9q2z</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/what-should-be-the-right-mindset-of-first-time-entrepreneur-k9q2z">&lt;p&gt;If you are the first time Entrepreneur then having the right mindset is very important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, It sound’s good if you have got an idea on which you want to work or if not then your first step is to think about an idea where you could simply work without being tired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having the right mindset of the first-time Entrepreneur is important because it keeps you motivated for the next task and holds your dream higher than anyone. Being an entrepreneur sounds cool but it takes lots of effort, hard work, and much more. I’ll try to keep it very simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-believe-in-yourself-and-dream-big&quot;&gt;1. Believe in Yourself and Dream Big&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to believe yourself first whatever you are going to do there are so many ups and downs. As long as you believe in yourself every difficulty will end up soon. You will stand up again with more power than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“One should never settle for less and always be ready to dream and achieve big!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-invest-your-time-wisely&quot;&gt;2. Invest your time wisely&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time is a very precious thing once it’s gone it will always begone. So, invest your time to sharpen your skills, read books, learn something new every day, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-learn-from-your-mistakes&quot;&gt;3. Learn from your mistakes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning from your past mistakes is one of the greatest skills. It keeps you one step ahead than you were yesterday and also keeps you away from doing the same mistakes. So, Don’t fear from your mistakes. Do it fast, learn from it, and stand on the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-be-communicative&quot;&gt;4. Be Communicative&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be shy or fear to communicate with others. If you are shy or have a fear of not able to communicate with others then you can’t learn some of the great lessons which come only to communicate with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-do-hardwork&quot;&gt;5. Do Hardwork&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never fear from doing hard work. Because it put you many steps ahead who just think and sit on the couch. Eventually, Doing Hardwork you developed the skill smart work. It’s one of my observations without doing any hard work you can’t develop smart work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey Entrepreneurs, hold your dreams higher than anyone. Your dream is yours not the others. Work like a hungry beast. Never settle for less, and one more thing Don’t give a shit to others.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Krishana Kumar</name></author><category term="Business" /><summary type="html">If you are the first time Entrepreneur then having the right mindset is very important.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Best Superhero and Scifi shows I found on Internet</title><link href="/article/best-superhero-and-scifi-shows-i-found-on-internet-dwbij" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best Superhero and Scifi shows I found on Internet" /><published>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/best-superhero-and-scifi-shows-i-found-on-internet-dwbij</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/best-superhero-and-scifi-shows-i-found-on-internet-dwbij">&lt;p&gt;Hey we all love to watch scify and superhero shows. Here is a list of my favourite shows. All of them are related to super power, heroes, science fiction, revolution and stuffs like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;series&quot;&gt;Series&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rick &amp;amp; Morty&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Agents of Shield&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Star Girl&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Super Girl&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Green Arrow&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Flash&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Titans&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iron Man Armoured Adventures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;movies&quot;&gt;Movies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iron Man&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avengers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Captain Marvel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I will add more to this list as i remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name>Anuroop Singh</name></author><category term="Super Hero" /><summary type="html">Hey we all love to watch scify and superhero shows. Here is a list of my favourite shows. All of them are related to super power, heroes, science fiction, revolution and stuffs like that.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What will it take to build a real Iron Man?</title><link href="/article/what-will-it-take-to-build-a-real-iron-man-shoc5" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What will it take to build a real Iron Man?" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/what-will-it-take-to-build-a-real-iron-man-shoc5</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/what-will-it-take-to-build-a-real-iron-man-shoc5">&lt;p&gt;It will take lots of resources and knowledge. But the best part is that it can be build.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anuroop Singh</name></author><category term="Super Hero" /><summary type="html">It will take lots of resources and knowledge. But the best part is that it can be build.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Age of Real Superheroes is coming</title><link href="/article/the-age-of-real-superheroes-is-coming-p8q3j" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Age of Real Superheroes is coming" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/the-age-of-real-superheroes-is-coming-p8q3j</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/the-age-of-real-superheroes-is-coming-p8q3j">&lt;h2 id=&quot;every-child-wants-superpowers&quot;&gt;Every child wants superpowers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our childhood most of us have fanticized about having superpowers. When we were child we all wanted to fly, to jump from high buildings without any injuries, to use those cool gadgets we saw in Ben10 and other really really cool scifi shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;over-time-the-reality-sank-in&quot;&gt;Over time the reality sank in&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sooner or later each one of use, as we grew we came to realization that super powers and heros are just fiction movie stuffs, they are not real and won’t be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-the-reality-we-accept-real&quot;&gt;Is the reality we accept real?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality that we accept, is it really real? I mean there are people who have been to moon, our satellites have reached beyond solar system, we are building advanced AI systems, we have really really advanced weapons system, sensor systems, strong materials, advanced electronics. Like, we have almost everythong to build a superhero’s arsenal. Why do we still think that superhero stuff can’t be real. Why do we believe so? Whenever i say “I have to become superhero”, normal people start laughing, i actually understand why they laugh. Well we have never really seen someone flying around, no super girl stuff, no iron man, no hulk smashing stuffs, not even spider man. At least we should have a real Spider Person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;when-i-found-iron-man-the-first-time&quot;&gt;When i found Iron Man the first time!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well all the credit goes to Iron Man. Thats the superhero i respect the most. All the inspiration behind all the tech and science and fiction and superhero stuffs that i will do in my life, all of it sparked that day, that moment, the first time Iron Man came out of that cave. Thanks Marvels. Thanks for inspiring a generation of humans, we will take us to &lt;strong&gt;Type 0 civilization&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Its ours turn to create the future of our civilization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Fiction is just a creation of human imagination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have seen superheroes only in movies, but the time is coming when real heroes with real superpowers will arise and so will super villains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wouldn’t you love to live in a future like that?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anuroop Singh</name></author><category term="Super Hero" /><summary type="html">Every child wants superpowers In our childhood most of us have fanticized about having superpowers. When we were child we all wanted to fly, to jump from high buildings without any injuries, to use those cool gadgets we saw in Ben10 and other really really cool scifi shows.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Futuristic Space Tech that will revolutionize space travel</title><link href="/article/futuristic-space-tech-that-will-revolutionize-space-travel-mlai2" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Futuristic Space Tech that will revolutionize space travel" /><published>2020-06-08T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-06-08T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>/article/futuristic-space-tech-that-will-revolutionize-space-travel-mlai2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/article/futuristic-space-tech-that-will-revolutionize-space-travel-mlai2">&lt;p&gt;What we are achieving in space using rockets is awesome. But these chemical rockets won’t take much deep into space. We need new tech that will take us faster and farther. Its clear not that in 2024 we will be on Mars, in 5 to 10 years we will have some kind of city on Mars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Farther and Faster is what we need&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-future-space-tech&quot;&gt;Some future space tech&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Nuclear powered rockets&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Atimatter Drive&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Blink Drive&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Warp Drive&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wouldn’t we feel thrilled if we could just go to our small spaceship parked somewhere near our house, enter it, it automatically turns on, we tell the AI where we have to go, the AI plots the course and off we go to the destination in deep space.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anuroop Singh</name></author><category term="Future" /><summary type="html">What we are achieving in space using rockets is awesome. But these chemical rockets won’t take much deep into space. We need new tech that will take us faster and farther. Its clear not that in 2024 we will be on Mars, in 5 to 10 years we will have some kind of city on Mars.</summary></entry></feed>