<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="/author/krishana/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2020-07-30T20:27:15+05:30</updated>
  <id>/author/krishana/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">LCF | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Creating Dream Worlds</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Rich dad, Poor Dad” advice to become rich?</title>
      <link href="/article/rich-dad-poor-dad-advice-to-become-rich-bfswl" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rich dad, Poor Dad&quot; advice to become rich?" />
      <published>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/rich-dad-poor-dad-advice-to-become-rich-bfswl</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/rich-dad-poor-dad-advice-to-become-rich-bfswl">&lt;p&gt;You often say sometime that you don’t want to live this kind bad life where you don’t live for yourself. You want freedom to live life as you want.
Everyone want to become rich ,live luxiourious life, travel around the world but they didn’t know where should they start or what should they do that could make him rich and became independent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here, is the &lt;strong&gt;“Rich dad, Poor Dad”&lt;/strong&gt; advice to become rich and earn more money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“True learning takes power, energy and burning desire and Anger is a big part of that formula”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Rich dad, Poor Dad, He primarily focus on 4 skills that make you to understand how the money works and after that you will become Independent. I’ll keep it super simple to understand what are these:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Accounting&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Investing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Understanding markets&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The law:
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Tax advantage&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Protection from lawsuits.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;accounting&quot;&gt;Accounting:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accounting is the financial literacy  or the ability to read numbers. this is most important skill if you want to become rich. The More you generate money, the more accuracy you required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;investing&quot;&gt;Investing:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the idea of ‘‘money making money”. This involve strategies and formula which multiply you money to make more money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;understanding-markets&quot;&gt;Understanding markets:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the science of supply and demand. In this, You need to know the technical aspects of the market which are emotion driven. Means, Does an investment makes more sense or not based ont he current market conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-law-&quot;&gt;The law:-&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The law is the awareness of accounting corporate, state and federal regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-tax-advantage&quot;&gt;1. Tax advantage:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this, A corporation can do many things than a person can’t  like pay expenses before pay taxes. Means in Basic terms, A rich man buy an “assest” first and then whatever is left on, they pay taxes on it while a normal person pay taxes first and live on what is left after pay tax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-protection-from-lawsuits&quot;&gt;2. Protection from lawsuits:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its s file folder with some legal document that creates a legal document in it. 
For example: when someone filed against a wealthy individual they are often met with layers  of legal protection and often find that the wealthy person actually owns nothing. they control everything , but own nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If, you really want to be rich the only thing you can do is expand your Knowledge. Knowledge in the field of financial terms. If you understand those terms soon you started  to realize that you grow your financial status. NOt so fast, but yeah! it’s started. and you continued to followed your dream path acheive whatever you want in life.
Remember, Knowledge is power. If you got this then YOu are the powerful one.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Krishana Kumar</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Business" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">You often say sometime that you don’t want to live this kind bad life where you don’t live for yourself. You want freedom to live life as you want. Everyone want to become rich ,live luxiourious life, travel around the world but they didn’t know where should they start or what should they do that could make him rich and became independent.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">What are the keys to start your own business?</title>
      <link href="/article/how-to-start-your-own-business-51qez" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What are the keys to start your own business?" />
      <published>2020-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-18T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/how-to-start-your-own-business-51qez</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/how-to-start-your-own-business-51qez">&lt;p&gt;Hey Entrepreneurs!!! 
Do you want to start something more creative that makes you different from the rest or you want to start the small  business. Everyone of you  have got their own idea. Your idea is in your mind, diary, and desk too and It’s flooded everywhere but you didn’t understand how did you get started with your own idea.  May be you think!! How did you get the capital for your idea, what are the requirements that fulfill your idea, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uhh f**k this!!!!!!! Don’t think too much that makes you feel horrible. In simple word’s due to your fear you didn’t start work on your own idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here, Some of the most important keys to start your own business. I’ll keep it simple. So, let’s start…….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Observation&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Understanding&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Apply it&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything is secondary if you didn’t start working on your own idea. So, don’t keep in mind. You’re smarter than you think you are. Just go and start work on your ideas because nobody gives you a damn shit about your ideas.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Krishana Kumar</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Business" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Hey Entrepreneurs!!! Do you want to start something more creative that makes you different from the rest or you want to start the small business. Everyone of you have got their own idea. Your idea is in your mind, diary, and desk too and It’s flooded everywhere but you didn’t understand how did you get started with your own idea. May be you think!! How did you get the capital for your idea, what are the requirements that fulfill your idea, and much more.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">What should be the right mindset of first time Entrepreneur?</title>
      <link href="/article/what-should-be-the-right-mindset-of-first-time-entrepreneur-k9q2z" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What should be the right mindset of first time Entrepreneur?" />
      <published>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/what-should-be-the-right-mindset-of-first-time-entrepreneur-k9q2z</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/what-should-be-the-right-mindset-of-first-time-entrepreneur-k9q2z">&lt;p&gt;If you are the first time Entrepreneur then having the right mindset is very important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, It sound’s good if you have got an idea on which you want to work or if not then your first step is to think about an idea where you could simply work without being tired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having the right mindset of the first-time Entrepreneur is important because it keeps you motivated for the next task and holds your dream higher than anyone. Being an entrepreneur sounds cool but it takes lots of effort, hard work, and much more. I’ll try to keep it very simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-believe-in-yourself-and-dream-big&quot;&gt;1. Believe in Yourself and Dream Big&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to believe yourself first whatever you are going to do there are so many ups and downs. As long as you believe in yourself every difficulty will end up soon. You will stand up again with more power than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“One should never settle for less and always be ready to dream and achieve big!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-invest-your-time-wisely&quot;&gt;2. Invest your time wisely&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time is a very precious thing once it’s gone it will always begone. So, invest your time to sharpen your skills, read books, learn something new every day, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-learn-from-your-mistakes&quot;&gt;3. Learn from your mistakes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning from your past mistakes is one of the greatest skills. It keeps you one step ahead than you were yesterday and also keeps you away from doing the same mistakes. So, Don’t fear from your mistakes. Do it fast, learn from it, and stand on the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-be-communicative&quot;&gt;4. Be Communicative&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be shy or fear to communicate with others. If you are shy or have a fear of not able to communicate with others then you can’t learn some of the great lessons which come only to communicate with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-do-hardwork&quot;&gt;5. Do Hardwork&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never fear from doing hard work. Because it put you many steps ahead who just think and sit on the couch. Eventually, Doing Hardwork you developed the skill smart work. It’s one of my observations without doing any hard work you can’t develop smart work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey Entrepreneurs, hold your dreams higher than anyone. Your dream is yours not the others. Work like a hungry beast. Never settle for less, and one more thing Don’t give a shit to others.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Krishana Kumar</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Business" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">If you are the first time Entrepreneur then having the right mindset is very important.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Best advice to become an Enterpreneur with no capital, connections, and experience?</title>
      <link href="/article/best-advice-to-become-an-enterpreneur-with-no-capital-connections-and-experience-suz8g" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best advice to become an Enterpreneur with no capital, connections, and experience?" />
      <published>2020-06-07T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/best-advice-to-become-an-enterpreneur-with-no-capital-connections-and-experience-suz8g</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/best-advice-to-become-an-enterpreneur-with-no-capital-connections-and-experience-suz8g">&lt;p&gt;You want to be an Entrepreneur, Of course, Yes!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it’s not then why are you here? It’s not for you, you should leave but if you want to become an Entrepreneur with no capital, connections, and experience then you are in the right place. I’ll keep it very simple and easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay So, let’s get started but first Tell me, How did Steve jobs start an entrepreneur journey without having any capital, experience, and connection?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How did Elon Musk start an entrepreneur journey without having any capital, experience, and connections? and there are many more interesting personality outside their that they have nothing when they start their journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My advice for a new entrepreneur with no real resources?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Embrace your job!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your job as an entrepreneur is to solve problems. See yourself as a puzzle maker. Entrepreneurship is actually the art and the science of putting the pieces together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No capital?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to think about how you can generate the capital for your&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No experience?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your job is to never stop learning, control your fear of failure, and learn from your mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No connections?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your job is to get out of your comfort zone and find the right kind of people that will lead you to achieve your goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Most importantly… #NeverGiveUp! 
As long as, You are not Give up and always ready to learn something new and learn from your past mistakes then there is no way that anyone can beat you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Krishana Kumar</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Business" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">You want to be an Entrepreneur, Of course, Yes!!</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
