<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="/author/anuroop/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2020-07-30T20:08:53+05:30</updated>
  <id>/author/anuroop/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">LCF | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Creating Dream Worlds</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Building our imagination in real world</title>
      <link href="/article/building-our-imagination-in-real-world" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Building our imagination in real world" />
      <published>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-07-15T14:30:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/building-our-imagination-in-real-world</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/building-our-imagination-in-real-world">&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-idea&quot;&gt;The Idea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our imagination we can create anything. 
We can build, rebuild, destroy any number of times. 
But is the real world we have always been limited. 
In the real world we lack the freedom to create anything we imagine. 
What if we can actually create the real world from scratch using just our mind? 
Will it be an exciting world? 
The world where anyone can build their dream world! 
Here we will build the tech that will allow us to do just that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;building-reality-step-by-step&quot;&gt;Building Reality: Step by Step&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of our imagination, there are many objects, living beings(trees, animals, humans, plants), roads, buildings, wind, water, machines, etc. Tech to create all of this can’t be build in one step. We propose that first step will be to build the infrastructure part (Buildings, roads, terrains, etc). Now complete buildings, roads, are very complex. So first step is to be able to build simple shapes like cuboid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-build-simple-structures-with-mind&quot;&gt;How to build simple structures with mind?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suppose, if there are some small blocks( maybe nanobots) that we can control from mind, and they can join together to build simple shapes (cuboid, pyramid, plane). For now we can build big blocks (few mm), that will self arrange into shapes when instructed by some machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parts-of-block-architecture&quot;&gt;Parts of block architecture&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Block can assume properties of any material. (Strength, lustre, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Control blocks with mind.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What will be the Structure and machinery of blocks?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Different types of connection leads to different levels of flexibility and strength.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Material of blocks?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;goal-1&quot;&gt;Goal 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 5 blocks. We build a simple structure in computer. There is some device that sends some EM signal to the blocks following some protocol. Upon receiving the signal, the blocks join together in the shape that we have build in our computer model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;further-goals&quot;&gt;Further goals&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reduce size of block.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Impoving connections between blocks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work on controlling blocks through mind&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improving security of software, so that only authorised person or machine can control the block.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blocks-as-universal-material&quot;&gt;Blocks as universal material&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No need to build different material for house, bridge, car, mat, chair, wire, etc. Over time blocks will become robust enough, they will be capable of assuming properties of any material and build anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can be used in construction of large scale structures in space without any 3D printers and human assistance. Machines will mine asteroids, produce blocks, blocks will join to build structures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like there is soil everywhere, what if there are these blocks everywhere and we can build anything with our minds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will make many 3D printers obsolete&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;easily-terraform-planets&quot;&gt;Easily Terraform Planets&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can send machines to other planets, deserts, etc, that will consume the resources available there and produce these blocks. We can then simple send instructions from here, and fully developed cities will be build for us in few days. Or we can simple go there and build whatever we imagine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sources-of-inspiration&quot;&gt;Sources of inspiration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nanobots, nanotech, Iron man suit in infinity war, MIT self joining bots, Neuralink, Exotic and special materials,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/hI5UDKaWJOo&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/hI5UDKaWJOo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mit.edu/2019/self-transforming-robot-blocks-jump-spin-flip-identify-each-other-1030&quot;&gt;Self-transforming robot blocks jump, spin, flip, and identify each other&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://people.csail.mit.edu/sclaici/pdf/romanishin20153d.pdf&quot;&gt;3D M-Blocks: Self-reconfiguring Robots Capable of Locomotion via Pivoting in Three Dimensions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mliWJ_HbQHQ&quot;&gt;Iron Man Suit Infinity War&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wevolver.com/wevolver.staff/m-blocks/&quot;&gt;https://www.wevolver.com/wevolver.staff/m-blocks/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.824.7275&amp;amp;rep=rep1&amp;amp;type=pdf&quot;&gt;M-Blocks: Momentum-driven, Magnetic Modular Robots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="New Ideas" />
      
        <category term="Robotics" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">The Idea In our imagination we can create anything. We can build, rebuild, destroy any number of times. But is the real world we have always been limited. In the real world we lack the freedom to create anything we imagine. What if we can actually create the real world from scratch using just our mind? Will it be an exciting world? The world where anyone can build their dream world! Here we will build the tech that will allow us to do just that.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Configuring mpv player - no border, loop and saving position on quit</title>
      <link href="/article/configuring-mpv-player-no-border-loop-and-saving-position-on-quit-e94bi" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Configuring mpv player - no border, loop and saving position on quit" />
      <published>2020-07-05T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-07-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/configuring-mpv-player-no-border-loop-and-saving-position-on-quit-e94bi</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/configuring-mpv-player-no-border-loop-and-saving-position-on-quit-e94bi">&lt;p&gt;mpv is one of the best video players on Linux. Its available on Windows and Mac also.  Lets find out how we can configure this awesome video player:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two different methods:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;command-line-set-everytime-you-use&quot;&gt;Command line (set everytime you use)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;no-border&quot;&gt;No border&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ mpv --no-border video.mp4
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;video-loop&quot;&gt;Video loop&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ mpv --loop video.mp4
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ mpv --loop video.mp4
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;edit-config-file-set-once-and-for-all&quot;&gt;Edit config file (set once and for all)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Using your preferred text editor (like vim), open the file &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/home/$USER/.config/mpv/mpv.conf&lt;/code&gt;. 
If this file does not exists, create it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add following code to the file &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;mpv.conf&lt;/code&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;loop=yes #Playing video will loop
border=no #Remove border
save-position-on-quit=yes #Save last position of playing video
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Save the file, close it, and restart mpv player.
Now it should be as you wanted. Enjoy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Tutorial" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">mpv is one of the best video players on Linux. Its available on Windows and Mac also. Lets find out how we can configure this awesome video player:</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">What are domain names, how do they work and how to get one</title>
      <link href="/article/what-are-domain-names-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-get-one-mwc9t" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What are domain names, how do they work and how to get one" />
      <published>2020-06-19T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/what-are-domain-names-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-get-one-mwc9t</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/what-are-domain-names-how-do-they-work-and-how-to-get-one-mwc9t">&lt;p&gt;We have seen lots of branded domain names like google.com, facebook.com . This site also have a domain name &lt;a href=&quot;https://letscreatefuture.com&quot;&gt;letscreatefuture.com&lt;/a&gt; . So what is the deal, and what are domain names, especially new domain names like .io, .photo, .website or even .me so much used these days?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this article, i want to explain what are domain names and answer some of the most common questions related to them. Here you will learn:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is a domain name?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is DNS (Domain Name System)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Difference between URL, domain name, sub domain, and domain extension.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are uses of domain names.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Where can you buy domain names&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-a-domain-name&quot;&gt;What is a domain name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the real world every house and location has an address, in the same way on internet a domain name is the address of your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Domain names are addresses of places on internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-do-we-need-domain-names&quot;&gt;Why do we need domain names?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want your own website, you are going to need a domain name. By entering the domain name in the browser someone will reach your website. Thats a address of your website which anyone can remember. Thats why people choose memorable domain names so that many people remember it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Your domain name is the first point of contact between you brand and your customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;example-of-domain-name&quot;&gt;Example of domain name&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some examples are www.google.com, emroline.com, facebook.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-do-domain-names-work&quot;&gt;How do domain names work?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using DNS domain names resolve yo IP address of the host that has the website running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-get-a-domain-name&quot;&gt;How to get a domain name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can go to any domain name provider website and buy a domain name. Some famous providers are godaddy, namecheap and epik.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a link for epik.com where you can buy domain names at cheapest possible price:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epik.com/?affid=mi1be1bi1&quot;&gt;Buy domain at lowest price on epik.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Tutorial" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">We have seen lots of branded domain names like google.com, facebook.com . This site also have a domain name letscreatefuture.com . So what is the deal, and what are domain names, especially new domain names like .io, .photo, .website or even .me so much used these days?</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Best Superhero and Scifi shows I found on Internet</title>
      <link href="/article/best-superhero-and-scifi-shows-i-found-on-internet-dwbij" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best Superhero and Scifi shows I found on Internet" />
      <published>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/best-superhero-and-scifi-shows-i-found-on-internet-dwbij</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/best-superhero-and-scifi-shows-i-found-on-internet-dwbij">&lt;p&gt;Hey we all love to watch scify and superhero shows. Here is a list of my favourite shows. All of them are related to super power, heroes, science fiction, revolution and stuffs like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;series&quot;&gt;Series&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rick &amp;amp; Morty&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Agents of Shield&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Star Girl&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Super Girl&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Green Arrow&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Flash&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Titans&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iron Man Armoured Adventures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;movies&quot;&gt;Movies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iron Man&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Avengers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Captain Marvel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I will add more to this list as i remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Super Hero" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Hey we all love to watch scify and superhero shows. Here is a list of my favourite shows. All of them are related to super power, heroes, science fiction, revolution and stuffs like that.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">The Age of Real Superheroes is coming</title>
      <link href="/article/the-age-of-real-superheroes-is-coming-p8q3j" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Age of Real Superheroes is coming" />
      <published>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/the-age-of-real-superheroes-is-coming-p8q3j</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/the-age-of-real-superheroes-is-coming-p8q3j">&lt;h2 id=&quot;every-child-wants-superpowers&quot;&gt;Every child wants superpowers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our childhood most of us have fanticized about having superpowers. When we were child we all wanted to fly, to jump from high buildings without any injuries, to use those cool gadgets we saw in Ben10 and other really really cool scifi shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;over-time-the-reality-sank-in&quot;&gt;Over time the reality sank in&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sooner or later each one of use, as we grew we came to realization that super powers and heros are just fiction movie stuffs, they are not real and won’t be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-the-reality-we-accept-real&quot;&gt;Is the reality we accept real?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality that we accept, is it really real? I mean there are people who have been to moon, our satellites have reached beyond solar system, we are building advanced AI systems, we have really really advanced weapons system, sensor systems, strong materials, advanced electronics. Like, we have almost everythong to build a superhero’s arsenal. Why do we still think that superhero stuff can’t be real. Why do we believe so? Whenever i say “I have to become superhero”, normal people start laughing, i actually understand why they laugh. Well we have never really seen someone flying around, no super girl stuff, no iron man, no hulk smashing stuffs, not even spider man. At least we should have a real Spider Person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;when-i-found-iron-man-the-first-time&quot;&gt;When i found Iron Man the first time!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well all the credit goes to Iron Man. Thats the superhero i respect the most. All the inspiration behind all the tech and science and fiction and superhero stuffs that i will do in my life, all of it sparked that day, that moment, the first time Iron Man came out of that cave. Thanks Marvels. Thanks for inspiring a generation of humans, we will take us to &lt;strong&gt;Type 0 civilization&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Its ours turn to create the future of our civilization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Fiction is just a creation of human imagination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have seen superheroes only in movies, but the time is coming when real heroes with real superpowers will arise and so will super villains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wouldn’t you love to live in a future like that?&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Super Hero" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Every child wants superpowers In our childhood most of us have fanticized about having superpowers. When we were child we all wanted to fly, to jump from high buildings without any injuries, to use those cool gadgets we saw in Ben10 and other really really cool scifi shows.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">What will it take to build a real Iron Man?</title>
      <link href="/article/what-will-it-take-to-build-a-real-iron-man-shoc5" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What will it take to build a real Iron Man?" />
      <published>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/what-will-it-take-to-build-a-real-iron-man-shoc5</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/what-will-it-take-to-build-a-real-iron-man-shoc5">&lt;p&gt;It will take lots of resources and knowledge. But the best part is that it can be build.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Super Hero" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">It will take lots of resources and knowledge. But the best part is that it can be build.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Futuristic Space Tech that will revolutionize space travel</title>
      <link href="/article/futuristic-space-tech-that-will-revolutionize-space-travel-mlai2" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Futuristic Space Tech that will revolutionize space travel" />
      <published>2020-06-08T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-08T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/futuristic-space-tech-that-will-revolutionize-space-travel-mlai2</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/futuristic-space-tech-that-will-revolutionize-space-travel-mlai2">&lt;p&gt;What we are achieving in space using rockets is awesome. But these chemical rockets won’t take much deep into space. We need new tech that will take us faster and farther. Its clear not that in 2024 we will be on Mars, in 5 to 10 years we will have some kind of city on Mars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Farther and Faster is what we need&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-future-space-tech&quot;&gt;Some future space tech&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Nuclear powered rockets&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Atimatter Drive&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Blink Drive&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Warp Drive&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wouldn’t we feel thrilled if we could just go to our small spaceship parked somewhere near our house, enter it, it automatically turns on, we tell the AI where we have to go, the AI plots the course and off we go to the destination in deep space.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Future" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">What we are achieving in space using rockets is awesome. But these chemical rockets won’t take much deep into space. We need new tech that will take us faster and farther. Its clear not that in 2024 we will be on Mars, in 5 to 10 years we will have some kind of city on Mars.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">How to go from 0 to billionaire?</title>
      <link href="/article/how-to-go-from-0-to-billionaire-ori16" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to go from 0 to billionaire?" />
      <published>2020-06-07T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/how-to-go-from-0-to-billionaire-ori16</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/how-to-go-from-0-to-billionaire-ori16">&lt;p&gt;Well as far as i have found there are certain steps or you can say jumps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-somehow-go-from-0-to-where-you-have-certain-money&quot;&gt;1. Somehow go from 0 to where you have certain money.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe noone starts from zero, they have almost nothing to began with but the resources they have can be used to generate some wealth. Like if you have a computer, you can write blogs, learn programming, do freelancing, build some websites and apps and sell them. Find people who need what you have and give your service to them in exchange for money. Save all the money possible. Like if you really want to be rich, at this stage get money from where ever you can. Learn from youtube videos about entrepreneurship. Learn and use your knowledge to earn money. Now its you job to figure out what and when to learn and how to use it. That what you have got a brain for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have enough money, so that you can work on your business plans move to step 2. Don’t end the step 1 hare. Work on your business idea and also do the side stuffs that will make you money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-use-the-money-to-build-small-business&quot;&gt;2. Use the money to build small business.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While building your own business for first time you will learn lots of new and useful stuffs, you will make many useful connections with all kinds of people and you will also make money. Save all of it the money, the people and the skills. They will prove to be pillars for your later stages. If you work on your business and it is successful, now you are getting enough money to survive. Now arising from this stage is again in your hands and brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-start-a-big-scalable-business-that-has-potential-to-transform-the-world&quot;&gt;3. Start a big scalable business that has potential to transform the world.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now use all the resources you have got to work on really big scalable businesses like the Amazon, Facebook, Google and lots of others that we keep on listening every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As your business will grow you will move to millionaire status and over time you will be multimillionaire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-work-on-solving-problems-that-are-so-difficult-that-nobody-else-could-even-think-about&quot;&gt;4. Work on solving problems that are so difficult that nobody else could even think about.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now its time to work on really hard and useful stuffs. Like Elon Musk is building Tesla and SpaceX, that kind of hard. Because now you have the money and power to pursue unrealistic &amp;amp; unimaginable goals, so this is the time to go for them. They will easily lift you to billionaire and world leader status if done successfully.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Business" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Well as far as i have found there are certain steps or you can say jumps.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">How to start a business from scratch?</title>
      <link href="/article/how-to-start-a-business-from-scratch-as24h" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to start a business from scratch?" />
      <published>2020-06-07T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/how-to-start-a-business-from-scratch-as24h</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/how-to-start-a-business-from-scratch-as24h">&lt;p&gt;Every great business starts with drive and passion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;six-steps-to-start-a-business-from-zero&quot;&gt;Six steps to start a business from zero&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-research-your-market&quot;&gt;1. Research your market&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should know deeply what the competition knows and thinks and feels. Dive in to your market and study it like an expert. Search google for keywords that are related to your industry. When you find the keywords flooded with websites, that means it works. There is money there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-set-tangible-goals&quot;&gt;2. Set tangible goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work backwords and figure out what you need to do each day to get to where you dream to be in the future when your business or startup is successful. Feel your success Here and Now. Set a goal that is a atretch for you and look at the steps you need to take everyday to accomplish that goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-launch-a-product-or-service-you-can-sell&quot;&gt;3. Launch a product or service you can sell&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a financial goal that you’ve set out for the next six months, then you have to sell something. Take the time to figure out the biggest challenges your audience is facing and build your relationship with them. Then create something that solves their problem. I know this is easier said than done, but it’s critical. Your leads come from your list, you convert them to customers, follow up and build a relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-start-now-and-improve-as-you-go&quot;&gt;4. Start now and improve as you go&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people waste time thinking about making things perfect before they launch their business. The logo, the website, the copy – everything. This is a waste of time. Sell your product before you make it by offering a pre-order. Focus on getting sales and attracting leads. Successful companies launch all the time and they aren’t perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of Facebook and all the changes and improvements it has made. Start with a small product and always be improving. Launch online you can sell over and over and not have to trade time for dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-create-a-great-website-whose-content-is-shareable&quot;&gt;5. Create a great website whose content is shareable&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s great to reference some the leaders in your space, but when you are developing your own brand, it’s important to create unique content on a single hub. A site that your readers and viewers can reference back to, for more of your incredible content. Maybe you can use wordpress or wix to get templates.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Business" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Every great business starts with drive and passion. Six steps to start a business from zero</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">How 5G will change the world?</title>
      <link href="/article/how-5g-will-change-the-world-kv0qi" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How 5G will change the world?" />
      <published>2020-06-05T00:00:00+05:30</published>
      <updated>2020-06-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
      <id>/article/how-5g-will-change-the-world-kv0qi</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/article/how-5g-will-change-the-world-kv0qi">&lt;p&gt;In our time we have experienced 2G, 3G and now 4G. With every successive generation, internet becomes much more reliable and faster. Now there is hype about fifth-generation connectivity or 5G internet. After all these years 5G is slowly coming to reality. This technology isn’t just going to change our lives, this is going to transform the entire human civilization. 5G has the potential to change everything. You should really get excited about this 5G thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_Qzc0dM9vTQ?rel=0&amp;amp;showinfo=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;so-what-is-5g&quot;&gt;So what is 5G?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well the ultra simplistic way to think about 5G is just an upgradation from 4G, but its quite a lot more than that. 5G will make networks more reliable and much more faster. 5G networks isn’t going to replace 4G, they’ll actually work side by side. 5G is fifth generation internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;but-why-should-i-care-about-5g&quot;&gt;But why should I care about 5G?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well we should care because 5G is just about to transform a lot of industries and that will impact all of us in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;well-here-are-the-top-ways-5g-will-change-our-civilization-forever&quot;&gt;Well, here are the top ways 5G will change our civilization forever:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;iot---internet-of-things&quot;&gt;IoT - Internet of Things&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT is real, its already here among us. Simply said, the things that are connected to internet are called internet of things. Like smart watch and shoes with various sensors.  With faster connectivity of 5G, more IoT devices will be available in our daily lives. 5G tech will enable companies to build products that can process data in realtime over internet much faster than currently possible. Improvements in IoT will make smart cities a reality. Reliable and low-latency network means traffic lights, fire sensors, camers all can be reliably connect over internet across cities, making the entire infrastructure smart and secure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;faster-gaming&quot;&gt;Faster Gaming&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyday with release of high quality real world like games, more and more people are spending time to play more games. The gaming industry is already big, and with the release of various Cloud gaming platforms, it is inevitable that the future will be bright for cloud gaming. With 5G, cloud gaming and game streaming will be much easier. 5G will bring more joy to the mobile game players due to faster response time, thanks to low latency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;virtual-and-augmented-reality&quot;&gt;Virtual and Augmented Reality&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VR and AR are already here you might think. But honestly they kind of suck, lets be real. To make something like augmented reality really great it takes a massive amount of data points and extremely low latency for your connections. So this is something thats tailor made for 5G. AR is the future. Imagine watching movies, serials and rocket launches in Virtual or Augmented Reality in your living room. How would you feel while playing some completely immersive VR game? With 5G and faster data transfers, users can experience content in their homes and feel like they are there in real.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;self-driving-cars&quot;&gt;Self Driving Cars&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driverless cars are here. You hear of Tesla? If not go and search, where were you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies like Uber, Tesla, Google, and now most probably Apple are investing in making the future of cars comfortable and driverless. Tesla has even pilot mode, which lets you give control to the Tesla car models and is improving day-by-day. Other companies are still testing it and are under continuous research and testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With 5G networks, ultra-low latencies will make it easy for cars to communicate with other cars. In order to avoid accidents, 5G will be a useful part. 5G networks will help in faster transfers. With these high-speed connections, sensors in cars can communicate with other cars around and become fully autonomous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will eradicate about 99% of read accidents. And in the coming future you will not be allowed to drive car yourself as that will pose a threat to a completely reliable and secure transport system thats secure and autonomous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;telemedicine&quot;&gt;Telemedicine&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With 5G, trips to your doctor may limit to house checkups. You will be able to talk to your doctor using internet. With HD calls, your doctors will be able to check your most health issues and recommend accordingly from home. They can check your vitals and other health-related details using the medical devices and wearables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remote surgery could mean that more people have access to the best doctors. But for that to be a reliable and widespread possibility again it requires massive amount of data being shared with ultra low latency. 5G will make that a possibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-about-a-5g-enabled-smart-farm&quot;&gt;What about a 5G enabled smart farm?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 5G enabled smart farm could be automated to the point that its able to produce even more food than whats currently thought possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;welcome-to-the-age-of-ultra-high-definition-live-streaming&quot;&gt;Welcome to the age of Ultra High Definition live streaming&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The age of streaming has finally come. With 5G, streaming will become more high-quality and can also mean that higher than 4K is coming to us. Since 5G is faster than 4G, it means it can stream better without lagging, which ultimately ends up in a better visual experience.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Anuroop Singh</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Future" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">In our time we have experienced 2G, 3G and now 4G. With every successive generation, internet becomes much more reliable and faster. Now there is hype about fifth-generation connectivity or 5G internet. After all these years 5G is slowly coming to reality. This technology isn’t just going to change our lives, this is going to transform the entire human civilization. 5G has the potential to change everything. You should really get excited about this 5G thing.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
